Your cabin
in the Singapore office is ready.
Did you see the photos?
The team's excited to meet you.
Soon, Vineet.
You know,
it could take two or three weeks
to hand over the Mukherjee case files.
Let me just remind you, Madam Tripathi,
that opening the Singapore office
was your idea, not mine.
I know, I know.
By the way, I miss you.
Me too.
What's wrong?
You seem a bit lost.
No.
I'm just thinking about
some old cases that got me this far.
Alright, I need to go now.
I'll call you later, okay?
Love you.
Yeah, me too.
Bye.
Hey, guys! I'm here at the Musafir Cafe.
And guess who I have with me here?
The founders themselves,
Chander and Preeti.
Well, this is a beautiful space
you guys have created.
- Thank you.
Tell me, how did you come up with
the name "Musafir Cafe"?
Actually, someone gifted me this name
many years ago.
- When this cafe was just a little dream.
- Wow.
And what about this famous promise wall?
Tell us what makes it so special?
- Good morning.
Slept well?
Come, sit.
You remembered?
I never forget anything, madam.
Especially not the opening day
of our cafe.
- Happy three to us.
Come here.
C, this is precious. I love it!
Happy?
C…
Sometimes, I think about
what would've happened
if we hadn't met five years ago
and lived together
during the lockdown.
You know this…
Yeah. Yeah.
Anyway, I was just thinking.
Mark & Nilima's home?
We can use it for the artist residency.
Really?
Yeah. I think it'll be perfect,
but you take your time.
Nervous?
Great.
A little nervousness before starting
anything new is great.
And I know what we exactly need
for this moment, so just hang on.
- Where are you going?
- One sec. One sec.
Let me do the honors.
Here you go.
I'm too good!
Thomas Bakery. Tripura. Same.
It's too good.
- We should do this more often.
- Yeah.
What are you thinking?
I'm not thinking, just…
Just reminiscing about…
the lockdown days,
stuck together in one room,
spending so much time with each other.
I would only talk about Musafir Cafe,
and you would talk about traveling.
You wanted to see Sri Lanka.
You wanted to go to Thailand
and learn scuba diving.
C…
the traveler in me hasn't died.
She's just taken a break for a while.
Yeah, I know.
What I mean to say is, you've made
Musafir Cafe what it is today, but…
promise me that you'll never compromise
on your dreams because of me.
Dreams can change too.
They can evolve.
Right?
Chander, aren't these beautiful?
Newlyweds, right?
I'll offer you a special rate of 550.
- Make it 350.
- Nothing less than 400.
The man's a newlywed.
How's he supposed to afford that?
Make it 380. Okay?
- Okay. Take it.
- Thank you.
Sir, a couple's photo?
- No, thanks, I have a camera.
- Sir, a couple's photo.
Look at this beautiful weather!
You're right.
We have to get a couple's photo.
Come on, we deserve one photo.
- What are you doing?
- The view is so lovely, Chander!
It'll be a great memory.
Sir, please move a bit closer to her.
How much closer?
Just a little bit.
What's wrong, Sharma ji?
Are you feeling shy?
That's more like it!
Now look at each other romantically, sir.
Romantically.
Sir, do you want one copy or two?
- Two.
- Okay.
This would make a beautiful location
for your cafe.
It's perfect.
Yeah, it's perfect here
right now, with you.
But for my cafe,
I'll find an even better place.
You're like the air my heart breathes in
Having you is all I need
No one else could do what you have done
The closer I get to you
The more I bloom
You've found your way
Into every part of me
I'm only a wanderer, just the same as you
How can I vow I'll never drift away?
And yet, my love, I've become yours
I've become yours, my love
I've become yours
My love
Oh, love of mine
- Oh, love of mine
- My love
I've become yours
My love
Okay, but what about
those two places we saw?
Okay, perfect.
Yeah, so how much will the rent be?
And the deposit?
Thank you. Thank you, Pankaj.
I'll call you back.
Looks like I'll be going back alone.
Not at all, madam.
I can't tell you.
It's all so clear in my head right now.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Wow!
Go ahead.
Pankaj, that broker we met?
He says we'll find something
in the next three months.
- What?
- Yeah.
I just have to take out a loan,
but the best thing is that
my boss is willing to be my guarantor.
Chander!
Yes!
Just imagine this, Sudha.
Your first cup of tea every morning
made by me, right here in these mountains.
It feels perfect, doesn't it?
You know, it already feels like
time has stopped here.
Like all the noise of the world has been
left far behind beneath these mountains.
Can I tell you a secret?
I've never been to the mountains before.
Really?
- Can I tell you another secret?
- Please.
This is my first trip ever with a guy.
Chander, I never even imagined that
I would wake up to a morning like this.
Imagine.
You and me,
right here in these mountains,
forever and ever.
Chander…
Breakfast is ready.
But no hurry. Take your time.
You were saying?
No. It can wait.
Good morning. How are you?
- Very well.
- Did you sleep okay?
- Yes.
- Mark?
- Yes?
- Jam?
Jam is on the table, love.
Okay, okay.
I have to just go quickly and come back.
- Hey!
- Hello, good morning.
- Good morning.
- Come.
- Oh, thank you.
- Start.
- Yeah.
You two are so cute together.
Really?
- Can I ask you two something?
- Yes, of course.
Have you two never thought about…
What? Getting married?
- Yeah.
- Good question.
I think we should just do it today.
Let's do it this evening.
You guys are also here.
What do you think?
No, I don't want to marry you.
See? This is why.
I learned this from my previous marriage.
That these legal papers, this society,
they can't bind two people together.
The only thing that binds is love.
And how did you two meet?
So…
after my ex-wife passed away,
I spent a few years with my kids
in California,
and then they left for college.
I didn't like being alone there.
So, I came to India. And as soon as
I got to India, I met her in Rishikesh.
And I never thought that, you know,
I could find love again.
But when I looked at her…
Yeah.
And I didn't care about society.
People can think whatever they want.
I still don't care.
But it takes a lot of courage
to make decisions like that, right?
I…
I chose myself.
Actually, our heart always knows
what's right.
Yeah.
It's the mind
that overthinks things later.
Yeah.
By the way, you know, his dream
is here in these mountains.
- Really?
- Yeah.
He wants to open his own cafe.
You two could even help him, right?
That's Mark's area of expertise.
Maybe he can help you.
- Happy to help.
- Thank you.
Opening a cafe sounds dreamy,
but running a cafe in these mountains
can beat you down.
Unless you know for sure
why you're doing it.
Yeah, I…
I understand
that mountains are tough.
But living someone else's life in the city
is far tougher, right?
And anyway,
here in the mountains, with Sudha,
I feel much more like myself now.
So, yeah.
The mountains don't change us.
They just show you
who you really are.
Yeah. So true.
What do you think, Sudha?
How do you feel here?
I…
I feel free.
But…
Your mountains are very beautiful.
That's true.
- So, you guys enjoy the breakfast.
- Thank you.
If you need anything,
you know where to find us.
- Sure.
- Alright.
- Come on, let's focus on lunch.
- Lunch?
Yes.
Chander, I didn't
want to tell you here, but…
I've accepted the job offer in Mumbai.
When?
Your mom was here,
and there was so much going on.
I just didn't get a chance to tell you.
And then after that, I was…
Chander, listen to me, okay?
It's the perfect opportunity.
I'm getting the opportunity to specialize
in civil disputes at the Family Court.
Big cases, a big law firm.
And the starting salary alone is more
than what I'd make in Bhopal in two years.
Can you imagine?
Just think about how much
I'd be able to do for Mom.
And, Chander,
all my dreams will come true.
Chander, I couldn't say no this time.
When do you start?
In three weeks.
Chander, you know…
if I had discussed this with you…
I don't think I could've
gone through with this decision.
And you know how important
this is to me, right?
Yeah.
So, we won't make any changes
to the downstairs spaces.
We'll… we'll retain its charm.
As for the first-floor rooms, we'll just
convert them into concept rooms.
And that's going to be
especially for artists and residents
who are here for a reason.
That sounds perfect.
I still can't believe you're leaving.
Since when did this guy
become so emotional, man?
Chander, I worry for you.
If you're so worried, then stay back.
By the way, I still feel you two
should use Nilima's and my bedroom
as one of the guest rooms.
- No!
- Why not?
No, we agreed.
That room will always be reserved for you.
- You'll come back as promised.
- But…
I've already donated this house
to the Musafir Cafe trust.
Uncle, you know that's not happening.
Okay.
As you wish. I resign.
But…
So, these are the papers. I signed them.
You keep them.
There's something--
I think I forgot something.
I'm forgetting something…
No, no, no. I'll go and check.
- Yeah?
- Yeah? Thank you, Preeti.
I need to talk to you.
You see, there's no one like Preeti.
She's at home here with you, right?
Yeah.
I have something for you.
- No.
- Why not?
- This is yours.
- No. It's Nilima's.
And I know how much she would have loved
for you to give this to Preeti.
She loved Preeti.
Preeti is a once-in-a-lifetime
kind of a partner.
You understand that, right?
- Hi. Missing something?
- Oh!
I forgot my passport! Oh my God!
I'm getting old, I guess.
Did you book the ticket?
What?
Did you book a ticket to Mumbai?
No.
First, I have to visit Mom,
wrap up some pending cases,
and then I will.
Ever since I told you about Mumbai,
you've been acting very weird with me.
Weird how?
Like I'm leaving you.
- You are leaving.
- No.
I'm just going to Mumbai, Chander.
Not Mars.
That's just something people say, Sudha.
Everything will be over.
What will be over?
I'll be there, you'll be here.
We'll meet on weekends and holidays.
We'll make it work.
Hey, Mr. America!
I'm not your ex.
We'll make it work.
Long-distance relationship.
Sudha, I've quit my job.
- What?
- Yes, I've quit my job.
Are you serious?
Oh my God, Chander!
I'm so proud of you!
You're going to Mussoorie
to open Musafir Cafe.
- I'm so--
- No, no.
Mumbai.
- What?
- Yes, Mumbai.
Look, I'm thinking,
I'll serve my one-month notice period,
and we'll get a fresh start.
I'll manage the house for a few days.
You can focus on your job.
And it's Mumbai, man.
I can easily find a new job.
One second.
You quit your job
to come to Mumbai with me?
Yes.
You're the one who always says
to follow your dreams.
Yes, Chander, follow your dreams!
Your dream isn't to work
a corporate job in Mumbai, right?
Your dream is to go to the mountains
and open a cafe, isn't it?
Yes, but you're my dream too, Sudha.
And dreams can change.
They can evolve.
Why can't two people's dreams merge?
I really thought you'd be happy.
It's my decision. I don't want this job.
- I'll go with you--
- What are you saying?
Chander, we just got back
from the mountains.
You were so happy there.
You shortlisted plans with Pankaj,
so how did this become
your plan all of a sudden?
I just want to be with you.
And is that really so bad?
Chander,
wanting to be together is not bad.
But moving your whole life to Mumbai
because of me is just--
Chander!
You don't like Bhopal,
you don't like Delhi,
you don't like Mumbai. You…
You were so happy in the mountains!
I felt it myself.
Go to Mussoorie
and open your cafe, Chander.
We'll manage. I promise.
One second.
We should get married.
What?
Sudha, think about it.
Think about it. This is perfect timing.
Mumbai, the job, marriage, a baby,
maybe this is how it's meant to be!
This is how it's meant to be, Sudha.
Marriage?
- Chander, what are you saying?
- No, I…
- Yeah, I-- I'm sorry.
- Marriage?
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry. I…
I'm sorry.
Fuck.
Sudha, wait a minute.
Just talk to me--
- No, Chander!
- Sudha…
Sudha!
Sudha, wait, at least talk to me!
Let go of me.
You're hurting me.
So, goodbye it is then.
For now.
No, but I'm really excited for you.
A new country, new adventures.
But no Preeti Kaushik.
All the best for your book launch.
And next year, Musafir House's
special room will be ready for you.
Promise me you'll write.
- My publishers are waiting.
- Only if you promise me to read it first.
- Deal.
Subtitle translation by: Neha Nair